

SIRAPUNSA THANGUTAIKUL

Human Resources

063-9262044

✓ sirapunsa115@gmail.com

Sirapunsa. T

Aspire Sukhumvit - Onnut - Bangkok, Thailand

ABOUT ME

I'm dynamic, responsible and highly adaptive and flexible.

I have experience in the HR function and my background knowledge in management.

I'm open to get new opportunity and bigger challenges. And I'm willing to learn new things.

My goal is I would like to grow in HR both HRM, HRD and share with others. And "discover a new experience"

SKILLS

Languages

- English
- Chinese

Soft skills

- Management
- Can do attitude
- · Team player
- Fast learner
- Communication

Hard skills

- · Microsoft Office
- G-suite, Zoom, Google meet, Gather Town
- Job post : JobsDB, Jobtopgun, Blognone, JobThai, JobBKK, Taskets, Jobfinfin / Social Media: Linkedin, Facebook

EDUCATION

Kasetsart university - Bangkok

August 2015 to May 2019

Bachelor's Degree in Political science GPA: 3.29

- · Volunteer of Rotaract KU Club
- Internship at BCP
- · Project coordinator: Stop Sexual Harassment

EXPERIENCE

HR Recruiter

Shippop Co., Ltd - Bangkok March 2021 to Present

Key Responsibilities:

- Handle overall recruitment process especially IT Positions of the company. (e.g. Developer, Tester, Data science, UXUI Designer, Tech Lead, PM etc.)
- Responsible for job posting, candidate screening, interviewing, scheduling, offering and onboarding new employees.
- Analyzing Job description & qualifications to understand the jobs roles and requirements of hiring managers.
- Preparing resume, portfolio, assignment, and other documents presented to hiring manager and HR Manager.
- Providing advice about the job requirement to candidates
- Managing the Internship Process
- Managing the employee evaluation
- Joined other activities relevant of HR team and Co-ordinate with internal and
- Supporting the other HR tasks as assigned

HR Officer

Builder Consultants Co., Ltd. - Bangkok January 2020 to February 2021

Key Responsibilities:

- Regularly update manpower (staffs at Construction Sites)
- Follow and prepare a document involved the site work such as minutes of meeting, Payment Certificate, Monthly Report etc.
- Responsible for administrative tasks (document- translate & draft etc.)
- · Handle overall recruitment process especially Engineers, Architectures,

Project Managers and Site Admin Officers for the company.

- Responsible for job posting, candidate screening, interviewing, scheduling, offering, negotiation and onboarding new employees.
- Analyzing Job description & qualifications to understand the jobs roles and requirements of hiring managers.
- Conduct the job evaluation and conduct the job contract and follow -up

CSR Officer (Internship)

Bangchak Corporation Public Company Limited (BCP) - Bangkok June 2018 to August 2018

I interned at BCP in CSR. I had a chance to learn a lot of responsibility such as managing projects and activities about CSR, coordinating and learning how to work with others as a teamwork etc. and I made new friends from other university.